Some see what's possible, others change what's possible.
Jobs is a drama, history film directed by Joshua Michael Stern.
The story of Steve Jobs' ascension from college dropout into one of the
most revered creative entrepreneurs of the 20th century.
Steve Jobs, played by Ashton Kutcher.
Steve Wozniak, played by Josh Gad.
Daniel Kottke, played by Lukas Haas.
Bill Fernandez, played by Victor Rasuk.
Chris Espinosa, played by Eddie Hassell.
Rod Holt, played by Ron Eldard.
Jobs is a 2013 American biographical drama film based on the life of Steve Jobs, from 1974
while a student at Reed College to the introduction of the iPod in 2001.
It is directed by Joshua Michael Stern, written by Matt
Whiteley, and produced by Stern and Mark Hulme.
Steve Jobs is portrayed by Ashton Kutcher, with Josh Gad as
Apple Computer's co-founder Steve Wozniak.
Jobs was chosen to close the 2013 Sundance Film Festival.
The film explores themes of computer, biography, based on
true story, entrepreneur, maniacal genius.
The tone is emotional.